http://intermountainhealthcare.org/website-information/privacy-notices/

Skip to Intermountain Healthcare company wide navigation
Skip to Intermountain Healthcare company wide footer navigation
Twitter
Intermountain Healthcare protects the privacy of your medical and personal information. We follow federal and state laws that govern the use of your health information and your personal information used on the website and personnel records.
Careers Privacy Notice
The online career application privacy statement explaining how certain personal information is collected, used and disclosed by the hosted web based application.
Learn More
Patient Privacy Notice
Privacy Practices Notice describing how medical information about you may be used and disclosed and how you can get access to this information.
Learn More
Protect Yourself From Scams
Intermountain Healthcare takes special care to protect your information. Protect yourself from criminal activities and avoid falling victim to scams.
Learn More
Website Privacy Notice
Privacy Notices and Terms of Use for the Intermountain Healthcare and SelectHealth websites.
Learn More
Get Care Now
Use Intermountain Connect Care®
Get care for low-level urgent conditions through a video chat with a provider, 24/7, on your computer or mobile device.Learn More.
Get in Line at InstaCare®
View wait times and save your place in line at an Intermountain InstaCare location near you.
Emergency Care
If this is an emergency please go to the nearest emergency room or call 911.
Which should I choose?
Intermountain
Healthcare
Intermountain Healthcare is a Utah-based, not-for-profit system of 24 hospitals (includes "virtual" hospital), a Medical Group with more than 2,400 physicians and advanced practice clinicians at about 160 clinics, a health plans division called SelectHealth, and other health services. Helping people live the healthiest lives possible, Intermountain is widely recognized as a leader in clinical quality improvement and efficient healthcare delivery.
Intermountain Blogs
Intermountain Facebook
Intermountain Pinterest
Intermountain Twitter
Intermountain YouTube
Contact Us
Tell Us About Your Experience
Get help with a billing issue
Still not finding what you are looking for?
Copyright ©2020, Intermountain Healthcare, All rights reserved.
